Contact

YA 555/12 BH 200 AVOCADOS STREET. +233599314620 (Mobile) abrahambaffoe317@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abrahambaffoe (LinkedIn) tothepointcode.com (Company)

Top Skills

Critical Thinking
Customer Satisfaction
Interpersonal Skills

Languages

German (Limited Working)
English (Professional Working)
Spanish (Elementary)

Certifications

Standford Center for Continuing Medical Education

Al Object Detection Engine Certification

EIT Industry "Augmented Virtuality" to Industry 4.0 and Beyond"

'Build Al Fake News Detection'
Online Bootcamp

Certificate of Participation

Honors-Awards
WHITE BELT
FACILITATOR & PHOTOGRAPHER

Abraham Baffoe

Virtual Assistant | Web Developer

Accra, Greater Accra, Ghana

Summary

I'm a Programmer and IT Analyst with four years of experience in Web Development, information security, technical support, Cloud Development, and software engineering. Jack-of-all-trades with broad experience supporting organizations voluntarily.

Proven experience in providing technical support to both hardware and software issues. Proficient in a wide range of technologies such as operating systems, Blockchain, and Al/ML.

Expert in all the available Microsoft suites, undoubtedly good in programming with Python, C++, R, HTML, CSS, JAVA, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Bootstrap, React Native, and Solidity.

Experience

DEXT TECHNOLOGY LIMITED GH

Distributor

September 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month)

DEXT Technology is a newly birthed innovative company in Ghana that produces the world's first portable, low-cost science set kits for all levels of educational use. The achievement of the DEXT is fantastic, awarded, and correlational parallel to satisfaction. The science set kits are a new tool to transition wards and folks into science and technology and appreciate nature, inspiring them to solve problems. They see the need for Science and technology today-tomorrow.

Dext
Distribution Specialist
October 2021 - Present (1 year)

Kumasi, Ashanti, Ghana

Education

Udacity

Foundation degree, Engineering (April 2022 - September 2022)

Albertus Magnus College
Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc, Pre-Medicine/Pre-Medical Studies

Xamk - South-Eastern Finland University of Applied Sciences Bachelor's degree, Game Development